aviva.com.sg 2017-12-23

# Privacy Policy - Aviva Singapore

### Overview

The Company is a member of the Aviva Group. We will use your personal details and information we obtain from other sources to provide you with our goods and services, for administration and customer services, to analyse your preferences, and to ensure that the content, services and advertising we offer are tailored to your needs and interests. We may keep your information for a reasonable period for these purposes. We may need to share your information with service providers and agents for these purposes. We may disclose personal data in order to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.We use cookies to collect information about how this Website is used. We use this information to improve how the Website caters for your needs and to identify any technical problems.

Cookies are small bits of data that are stored by your browser. You can accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings of your web browser. Further details are available in the Company's Cookie Policy or for further information about how to disable cookies in your browser please visit the [About Cookies Website.](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

When you visit our Website, we may also log your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device.

If you have provided your personal details to a member of the Aviva Group or its business partners, the data protection notice given to you at the time will continue to apply and you may therefore be marketed to under the terms of that notice.

The Internet is worldwide and if you are visiting this Website from outside Singapore your visit will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international borders. By visiting this Website and communicating electronically with us you are consenting to these transfers.

If you provide us with information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed you to act for them and to consent to the processing of their personal data including sensitive personal data, and that you have informed them of our identity and the purposes (as set out above) for which their personal data will be processed.

We link to a wide variety of other websites and we display advertisements from third parties on our Website. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these websites and third party advertisers, nor for the way in which information about their users is treated. In particular, unless expressly stated, we are not agents for these websites or advertisers nor are we authorised to make representations on their behalf.

You are entitled to ask for a copy of the information we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to have any inaccuracies in your information corrected. To do this please write to us at the following address:

**For Aviva Ltd customers:  
**Aviva Ltd - Customer Services   
4 Shenton Way , SGX Centre 2   
#01-01, Singapore 068807   
Tel: 6827 9933   
Fax: 6827 7480

**For Navigator Investment Services Ltd customers:  
**Navigator Investment Services Ltd - Customer Services   
4 Shenton Way , SGX Centre 2   
#01-01, Singapore 068807   
Tel: 6827 7555   
Fax: 6827 7700

For quality control and training purposes, we may monitor or record your communications with us. The data protection notice may change and therefore you should review it regularly. We will of course notify you of any changes where we are required to do so.

For information on Aviva's personal data protection policy, please visit [www.aviva.com.sg/pdpa.html](http://www.aviva.com.sg/pdpa.html)

Back to top 

### Cookie Policy

Protecting our customers is at the heart of everything we do at Aviva and protecting your information is no exception. This means that any cookies used on our sites will not contain personally identifiable information about you. However, we do use cookies on our websites to help make your visits more effective so we’d like to explain more about how and why we use them.

**Cookies make websites work better**  
Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by websites or sometimes by emails. They allow you to use the site more efficiently and save time by not having to re-enter your details each time you visit. They also make sure you receive the most relevant information from Aviva. For us, cookies help us to analyse how our customers interact with our sites so we can make improvements. Some cookies are essential and some are not.

**Essential cookies**  
Session and Tracking cookies  
Certain cookies are necessary in order for you to use our websites, such as maintaining log in details for the session or a transaction.  These are used only for the duration of each visit, and they expire when you leave the site. They’re not stored on your computer and they don't contain any personal data. You can delete them via your browser if you wish to, but this will restrict the functions that you're able to carry out on our sites. Session and Tracking cookies are commonly used, you can visit the [About cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)  website for more information.

**Flash cookies**  
These cookies make it quicker and easier for you to access sites on subsequent visits that use Flash technology. Deleting them means you may have to re-enter information each time you visit the same site. But just like any cookie, you can delete Flash cookies by going to the Settings Manager for your Adobe Flash Player. You will be taken to the Adobe website, which lists the websites with the cookies in your browser. Just click Delete opposite the relevant website.

**Non-essential cookies**  
These cookies are usually supplied by our business partners. We use some non-essential cookies for analytical and marketing purposes.

Online Advertising cookies  
Provided by our online advertising suppliers, these cookies are used to serve our internet advertisements on other sites. Some of our web pages may contain electronic images that help us see how users interact on these pages. They may also provide our online advertisers with information about the interaction.

Web Analytics Tools  
From time to time Aviva uses certain web analytics tools. These web analytics services enable us to recognise repeat visitors to the site. By matching an anonymous, randomly generated identifier, we’re able to record specific browsing information such as how you arrive at the site, the pages you view, and the path you take through the site. By monitoring this information we’re able to make improvements to our sites.

**You can accept or block cookies**  
By using our websites you agree that we can place both essential and non-essential cookies on your device. At any time, you can block any cookies from any website through your browser settings. Do take note that if you share the use of a computer, accepting or rejecting the use of cookies will affect all users of that computer.

Back to top
